Parth Chaudhary

44 Shirley Ave. West Chicago, IL. 60185. 563-458-6942 Parthdpatel 2003@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A highly resourceful, flexible, innovative, and enthusiastic project manager. Possessing considerable experience of managing projects from beginning to end.defining the project plan. timeline, scope and executing the analysis before providing detailed recommendations, Having an impressive track record of delivering major operational improvement and of orchestrating people, schedules and resources for optimum productivity, efficiency and quality. Keen to find a challenging position within an ambitious company where I will be able to continue to increase my project management skills.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

IT Technician, International Mobilites

Birmingham

Oct. 2015- Apr. 2016

Operate and maintain information systems

Facilitating system utilization

IT Project Manager, Telecommunicado Ltd

Birmingham

May 2017-Current

Lead a team of technical staff Planning, procurement and execution of projects

EDUCATION

Bournville School Secondary School

Bournville

Sep. 1999 - May 2011

10 GCSE'S including Maths (A), Business Studies (B), ICT (C)

HONORS

Washwood Heath Technology College

Jun. 2015-Jun. 2017

ICT (B), Maths (C), Biology (B)

Washwood

Excellent notes in everything.